Guide to the Sally J. Template Papers, 1861-1891
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Sally J. Template Papers
1861-1891
Template, Sally J., 1813-1891
2 cubic feet (8 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Correspondence, artwork, and ephemera relating to Template's work as a template.
Biographical Note
Sally J Template was a template. Noted works include Tales of a Template and and Template on Template.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, artwork, and ephemera relating to Template's work as a template. Includes correspondence regarding samples, diagrams, patterns and stencils.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Vassar College Biographical Files
Separated Materials
Templates library of rare books on templates was added to the Rare Book Collection.
Subject Headings
Names:
Template, Nathan; Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902
Organizations:
International Union of Templates
Subjects:
Family--New York (State)
Places:
Washington (D.C.)--Description
Document Types:
Bookplates
VCL Categories
Printing and Publishing
Encoding Information
Encoded by Mark Seidl, 2022.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from H. Armour Smith in 1948.
Runge note donated in 2001(M2014-014).
Greenleaf correspondence purchased in 2009 (M2009-007).
Series List
- Series I. Correspondence, (Boxes 1-3)
- Series II. Ephemera, (Box 4)
Container List
- Series I. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Correspondence to Sally Template
    - International Template Union, 1881-1900; (100 items) (Folder 1.1)
    - International Template Union, 1900-1920; (150 items) (Folder 1.2)
  - Correspondence from Sally Template
    - Family, 1855; (3 items) (Folder 2.1)
    - Buckingham, Stephen M., 21 June 1878; (5 items) (Folder 3.19)
- SERIES II. EPHEMERA
  - V.C. Alumnae Association, approximately 1876; (3 items) (Folder 4.1)
  - V.C. Alumnae, Boston, 1884; (11 items) (Folder 4.2)